Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
What's the matter?
It's fine.
Oh, my God.
He...
he blocked that hit with his helmet!
That's incredible!
A couple of inches left to ride
and it would've killed him!
What an incredible fight, huh?
Every one of those attacks
is aimed at some vital spot.
Just one slip from either
of them and that's it.
They're dead.
These guys have really been
fighting to the death for 100 years?
That's got to get old.
This is a good thing.
This is our chance to get away. Let's go.
Usopp?
Amazing.
Why?
I don't remember.
They fight so seriously, and
they don't even know why.
This fight's getting really annoying.
Don't you see?
This is an example of a real
battle between real men.
Hmm?
Say what?
Maybe an analogy will help.
It's as if they have each planted a flag
in their hearts that says, I am a warrior.
This flag is more important than
anything, more than their lives even.
They can never allow the flag
to be destroyed by someone else.
That's why they both continue
this fight for a hundred years.
Do you see it now?
This is a proud duel.
A legendary fight between
two dedicated warriors.
Yeah, whatever.
That warrior stuff doesn't really
interest me in the slightest.
You coming.
No, I'm still watching this.
This is my ultimate goal.
This right here.
To be a brave warrior
like each of these titans.
Really though, someday.
I will be a proud warrior of the sea.
So what you're saying then?
Is that you want to be a giant?
Moron!
You haven't listened to a
single word I've said, have you?
Hey, Usopp Isn't there something
that you're supposed to be watching?
If there's a village full
of warriors like these two,
then I really want to go there someday.
It's safe to say that we're both
starting to get homesick here.
Ah, Dory.
That's why I intend to
win this duel of ours.
I'm going to beat you
and go home to Elbath.
Got that, Broggy?
73,466 duels.
Hey, if you're done, get out of the way.
Wait, I can handle this.
3,000 telegram press!
Oh, hello, Mr. Five.
I'm impressed by the decor.
You have a talent for turning even the
most savage environment into a home.
I admire you, which is why I feel
compelled to remind both of you.
This mission belongs to
me and Miss Valentine.
Rest assured, we won't slip
up like we did last time.
Slip up?
That's not why I'm here,
Mr Five, Miss Valentine.
The simple fact of the
matter is you are both weak.
Don't waste your energy pouting.
It is what it is.
Take a look at this.
I'd like to thank you both for affording
me an excuse to come to this island.
I'll enjoy the opportunity to hunt.
some truly big game.
Dory the Blue Ogre and Brogy the Red
Ogre are the giant warrior pirates.
Everyone's heard of them.
It's ancient legend.
Hey, this poster's over 100 years old.
Well, those two legends are alive
and well on this very island,
battling over a century now.
Back when that poster was new,
the bounty on their heads was
100 million berries apiece,
200 million for the both of them.
200 million berries is an impressive sum.
but that doesn't change the
fact that they're giants
there's a wise saying
superior criminals are those
who execute their crimes
using superior intellect
all you have to do is follow
my precise instructions
with a smidgen of forethought
and perseverance you
can find the solution to
even the most gargantuan of?
...of obstacles.
Hey, Dory, a couple of guests
of mine gave me some alcohol.
Drinks?
It's been a long while.
Hey, Brogy?
That's interesting.
So Bragi's guests are
friends of yours, then.
I saw a goofy-looking guy with
a long nose and a woman there.
That's Usopp and Nami.
They said they weren't even
gonna get off the ship.
I guess they wanted to have
an adventure after all.
If they're your friends,
then I guess I can thank you,
too, for these yummy refreshments.
So, Dory, tell us, does it really take a
year for the log to reset on this island?
Yes.
You notice all the mounds of human
skeletons that are lying around here?
I guess it's hard not to.
The people who come to this island tend
to die before their logs are reset.
Some become dinosaur food.
Some die from heat or
thirst or starvation.
Others are killed because
they stupidly attack us.
Whatever the case, they
all die here somehow.
An entire year on this island
just seems to be too long.
So far, no humans have been able
to survive here for the full year.
What are we going to do?
Even if we could manage
to last here for a year,
who knows what could happen by then?
My country could be lost.
She's right.
Plus, I get bored here after a year.
Isn't there anything else
we can do about it, old man?
Hmm.
We do have an eternal pose here,
but its magnetic link is to
our home village, Elbath.
Basically,
that eternal pose is
what Broggy and I have
been fighting for with
our duels this whole time.
Of course, you can try
to take it by force.
No, that's not gonna work.
Elbaf isn't the place that
we're trying to get to.
We just want to get to the island
that's right after this one, right?
Yes.
We must stay on the route that's
going to lead us to my home,
or else there's no point.
Yeah.
Maybe you can try
sailing forward randomly.
You may get there eventually.
If you're real lucky.
Maybe so.
We may actually get there.
Now that I think about it,
someone did leave the island
once before his log was reset.
And what happened to him?
How should I know that?
I'm sure he was able to
get to the next island.
That must be it.
What is so funny?
I don't understand what these two idiots
are laughing about at a time like this.
A brave warrior of the seas, you said.
What's that exactly?
I'm talking about you guys.
What I really want is to be
like the two of you some day.
Huh?
You want to be a giant?
You hear that?
That's not what I mean!
I want to be a great warrior.
I want to be brave and proud like
you and the others from Elbath.
I see.
You know, in Elbath, even though our
lifespans are longer than yours are,
we still think about how we will die.
We know everything we have and everything
we are will one day cease to exist,
like everything else.
But it is worth it to die a true warrior
of Elbath, without sacrificing your pride.
That is what we call dying with honor.
To die such a great death would
be an everlasting treasure.
It's what we seek in Elbath.
So pride is your treasure.
That's great.
I've decided to learn from you.
From now on, I'll call you Master.
Huh?
Oh, giant guy!
What's going on?
Why did it explode?
That was the same alcohol
we had with us on the ship,
wasn't it it exploded in his stomach the
other giant must have booby-trapped it
hold it were you even watching them they
fight their duels honorably
no way he'd do that
all right then who did do it
You strangers!
That wasn't Froggy!
No way!
No warrior of Elbaf would dare!
So, who else is there to
suspect on this island then?
Besides you!
Let's get out of here!
There's no use talking to him right now!
I doubt running would do us any good.
Hold on to this! Stay back!
You're going to...
fight Dory?
Yeah, I don't want to.
But we have to settle this.
Don't do it, you guys! Stop it!
Dory, please just listen to me!
We don't know anything about the
explosives in the barrels, I promise!
We wouldn't do that!
You can't be in any shape to
fight right now, so please stop!
Right.
Why should I believe you liars?
All right then, Gum-Gum!
GUNGUNFUL!
Sorry…
BROCKER!
No! Luffy!
He has some power from
one of the devil fruits.
It seems I underestimated him.
Luffy are you all right how is he he
should be okay i guess you were right
about fighting He's certainly a lot
calmer now well i'm not the old guy was
right about one thing anyway The other
giant would never do anything like
this but i know that our friends wouldn't
do it either They aren't like that.
Yeah, then who?
There must be somebody
else on this island.
The key to winning any game is to
know your opponent's state of mind.
For now we have succeeded
in confusing our enemy.
They are no doubt wondering about the
mysterious bomb that we delivered.
And about the identity
of their invisible enemy.
Our first target was the
long-bearded giant Dory.
I knew, of course, that it would be
nearly impossible to finish him off,
but the damage done to his stomach by
the bomb must have been considerable.
Now,
we can sit here enjoying our tea while
relaxing and wait for the next duel to start.
So we stay in the background and let
the giant kill off the injured one?
Yes, that's exactly right.
That's certainly an indirect method.
Again, you have to consider your enemy.
Warriors like these two operate in
much the same way as wild boars.
They can be intimidating
in a head-on fight,
but they don't have the brains to think
beyond their immediate circumstance.
So why bother going after
them directly when you
have the intelligence to
destroy them indirectly?
Hmm?
Hmm.
Why can't you just get
the tea yourself, Ms.
Geldenweek?
And just what are we supposed
to do with the Straw Hat Gang?
Straw Hat Gang?
Oh, you're talking about the little
brats who found out the boss's secrets.
We can start by luring
them out one by one.
The order doesn't matter, really.
Let's start with the one
closest to my tea set.
I have a personal motto, you know, and
that is big crimes via cheap tricks.
There are plenty of good ways to
defeat any enemy, all without fighting.
That's their signal, isn't it?
Well, there's the signal.
It's really been active today.
You're really going?
But your wounds from the
last battle haven't healed.
Please, Dory can't be
doing any better than me.
A few scratches won't
take me out of a duel.
That would sure make me a poor
excuse for a brave warrior.
Wait, giant guy.
Don't.
You can't fight, Dory.
You need to rest.
You'll die if you push yourself too hard.
I will fight.
I am Dory.
I will fight for Elbaf's
pride and die as a warrior.
Now, Mr.
Broggy, go and show this guy.
You bet, Usopp.
I'm going to beat him for sure this time.
He hasn't got a chance.
Go get him, you great warrior of Elbaf.
The mighty Broggy always
defeats his opponent!
You can do it, Broggy!
You're the mightiest warrior in the world!
You can destroy him any day!
You're gonna crush him!
Go, warrior Broggy!
Fight like the proud warrior you are, Mr.
Broggy!
Why does it continue this pointless fight?
How can you say something
like this is pointless?
Broggy is a brave warrior,
just like I'm gonna be someday!
You have no right to
say anything, you idiot!
Well, now we can think about
getting back to the ship.
Waiting for a year,
there's no freakin' way.
It's completely unacceptable.
We need to get everyone back on
the ship and come up with a plan.
Now, hold on a second.
I, for one, don't think we stand a
chance in a fight against dinosaurs.
Cutting through the jungle
in order to get back to the
Mary won't do us much good
if we get killed on the way,
will it?
What happened to all that brave warrior of
the sea stuff you've been going on about?
I said that someday I would
be a brave warrior of the sea.
Besides, even a brave warrior has to have
enough sense not to get himself killed.
We don't have a choice here.
Luffy's group is over at
the other giant's place.
We should probably head that way first.
Nami, listen, even if I should
lose everything someday?
and I must face a horribly tragic
death, alone on a deserted island,
I will proudly say this
about how I have lived.
I am Captain Usopp and know that I have
been a great brave warrior of the sea!
Yeah, yeah, but for now, do you think you
could just try to be a dependable warrior?
Right. Let's go!
Come on, what are you doing?
Get this rock off me, move this thing!
It's been over a century.
Since we started the battle, this duel!
Injured or not, I cannot allow
myself to run away from this fight.?
To do so would be like running
from the title of warrior.
And if I was no longer a warrior of Elbath,
then I would no longer know who I am.
I'm sorry I suspected you
of causing the explosion.
I now know that this was a judgment.
A judgment from Elbath, the god of war.
I didn't have the god's
protection, and that is all.
Listen to me!
Gods and protection and judgments have
nothing to do with what's going on!
If a god told you to just
run off and die, would you?
Someone has interfered with your duel!
And a duel that's been interfered
with isn't a fair fight anymore!
Isn't that right?
Silence!
What can you know about this?
You're a human who can't have been living
on this earth for more than two decades.
How can you possibly hope to understand
the ways of the warriors of Elba?
Who cares about that stuff?
Get this damn thing off me! Hey! Oh, God!
Listen to me!
Move this rock already! Come on!
Come back here!
You can't leave me trapped like this!
Dory, how was your drink?
Hit the spot, didn't it?
Yes!
It tasted almost godly!
Well, I'm glad that you enjoyed it.
Let's go.
Move, you stupid rock! Come on!
Of course!
Just what I mean a great
warrior, this happens!
Just calm down.
I don't understand why he's so
upset over someone that he just met.
He sure doesn't seem much like a hardened
criminal with a bounty on his head.
Who was it?
Who would dare to interfere?
I'll kill them!
Hey, Luffy.
Karu's missing.
This isn't good.
I'm lost.
This tree looks familiar, but it's
kind of hard to tell in this place.
I think I was supposed to take a
left at the tree wrapped in vines.
Oh, hey, Nami, it's you.
Seems like I got lost.
Looks like you got some
pretty good timing.
I wasn't sure what I was going to do.
So, what are you doing
in this area anyway, huh?
Uh, Nami?
Oh crap, it's another dinosaur!
Usopp, wait up!
Luffy!
Boy, is it a relief to see you!
So what are you doing here anyway?
Eh?
Huh? Nami?
Nami! Nami! Nami!
Where did she go?
ZOMBIE!
There is a treasure out there to be found.
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big
place, the oceans are wide.
The muck and bone won't help you find it.
Just give up the task when I'm become?
Even so!
If someone tries to be
fast from moving home!
The factor behind the
back just keeps us strong.
It's too bad cause we're still
selling for what's so fun for ya!
Just leave us alone.
It may be foolish chasing
impossible things.
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream, the
more ambition I'm gonna need.
It may be foolish driving on!
But I know that I just gotta try.
Far through the sea, the great
of paradise, we've got to find.
Don't give up, just keep on trying,
and you'll see that you're closer to?
The horizon of your dreams.